Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Mammal Hero
I also want to draw the ultimate hero manga!
What's wrong?
He said the manga he read was so interesting
that he wants to draw one himself.
But I can't think of a good character.
In that case, welcome to...
THE WORLD OF SERIOUS PALEOTOLOGY!
Hey, Dino.
How about getting hero ideas from prehistoric creatures?
I see!
Then modern animals would also be great, right?
Yes.
But aren't prehistoric creatures better?
No, no,
modern animals are definitely better!
Then let's have a showdown to see which creature is better
suited for a hero character!
Battle!
First strike wins!
How about the African elephant?
It has thick and tough skin,
and enough power to lift a car
a super strong hero!
Ooh, that sounds cool!
An African elephant, huh?
If so,
long tusks...
a mammoth would feel much more like a hero!
Covered in body hair from head to toe,
it can withstand any freezing cold...
a fluffy hero!
Eh?
A hero whose strength is resisting cold?
A Woolly Mammoth, is it?
That's interesting!
Then how about a modern creature...
.like a lion?
Catching prey with sharp claws,
it's known as the King of Beasts...
a mane hero!
A king and a hero?!
That's awesome!
Male lions are basically free-loaders, you know!
Eh?
The females do most of the hunting,
and the males just live off their prey!
Instead of that,
how about a prehistoric saber-toothed cat?
Specifically speaking, what about Smilodon?
With cool tusks
and powerful forelegs,
it's a saber hero!
No wait, it's drooling!
Why won't it close its mouth?
Smilodon can open its mouth up to 120 degrees!
In that case...
I push for a modern animal: the kangaroo!
With over 50% of its body made of muscle...
it's a muscular hero!
Eh?
Its suit is falling off though?!
It's a good idea but,
Smilodon's tusks won't lose either!
Objection!
Smilodon's tusks are long,
so they break easily, right?
Wh-What?!
Dino using prehistoric knowledge?!
A hero's tusks and heart of justice...
WILL NEVER
BE BROKEN!!!
Well said! That sounds so cool!
You...
When did you
get so knowledgeable about prehistoric creatures?
I've been
studying every single day too!
I'm taking on the challenge with an undaunted fighting spirit!
Dino...
What's with you all of a sudden?
Perhaps there's no longer any need to insist on choosing between modern or prehistoric creatures!
between modern or prehistoric creatures!
President?
Why don't we create it together?
Combining both our ideas
into one ultimate creature-respecting hero!
Yes!
The power of an African elephant!
The thick fur of a Woolly Mammoth!
The mane of a lion!
The jaw of a Smilodon!
The muscle of a kangaroo!
This is our...
ideal hero!
Scary!
Cramming all that together makes it look scary!
I mean...
no matter
how you look at it, isn't that a villain?!
Thank you for your support during this short time!
Please look forward to Dino-sensei and Tetori-sensei's
next work!!
Plannosaurus Serious Paleontology Club... To be continued.
Next time, the anime final episode: 'Serious Mata-Kamen's Trial'.